Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory7 Mss.B.B61.inventory07
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents K
  - Knopf, Alfred A. (Box 52)
    - A.A. Knopf -- from P.B. Thomas, 1926 Jan. 27
  - Knopf, Olga (Mrs. Alfred A.) (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 9; 1p.
  - Knott, Sarah Gertrude (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 16; 1p.
      (Enc: Tentative program)
  - Knowles, F.H. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 22
  - Knox, George William (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 13
  - Knox, Lucy P. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1929 Mar. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 24; 2p.
    - L.P. Knox -- to G.A. Reichard, 1931 May 20; 2p.
    - (Enc. originally with Reichard, G.A., July 11, 1931)
  - Knox, Owen A. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1940 June 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - See Bollens, John H., Feb. 6, 1940.
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 15; teleg.
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 June 21; 1p.
    - (Enc: Blank), 1940 June 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 19; 1p.
    - O.A. Knox. -- to M.E. Woolley, 1940 Aug. 6; 1p.
    - (Attached to Woolley, M.E., Aug. 1, 1940)
  - Knox, P.C. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 1; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 4; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 5
  - Knudsen, Martin (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 8; 1p.
  - Kny & Scheerer Corp. of America (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Sept. 27
      See Lagar.
  - Kober, A.W. (Box 52)
    - A.W. Kober -- to W. Heinitz
      - See Heinitz, W., Dec. 24, 1929.
  - Koch, E. (Box 52)
    - E. Koch -- to United German Societies. Executive Committee, 1933 Sept. 21; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Brenstorck, V.M., Sept. 26, 1933)
  - Koch, F.J. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 23
  - Koch-Grünberg, T. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1923 May 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Sept. 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 26; 2p.
  - Kock (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar.; 3p.
  - Koebe?? (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 27; 1p.
  - Koebisch (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 3; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Kallmann, Franz, Oct. 26, 1936)
  - Koechl, Paul (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 28; 1p.
  - Koechl, Victor (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 17; 1p.
  - Koedel, S.G. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 8; 2p.
  - Koehler, Hugo A. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 21; 2p.
  - Koempel, Franz (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 12; 1p.
  - Koenig (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1905 June 3
  - Koening, O. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1909 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 30
  - Koettgen, J. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1917 Sept. 25; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct.; 2p.
  - Kohan, S. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 6; 1p.
  - Koher?, Wolfgang (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1936 May 15; 1p.
  - Kohl, O. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 11; 2p.
  - Kohler, A. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 July 17; 3p.
  - Kohler, Frischersen? (Box 52)
    - F. KC6hler -- to R. Lehmann, 1919 Nov. 24; 3p.
  - Kohler, Max J. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1934 May 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 May 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 16; 1p.
  - Kohn, Robert D. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Sept. 13; 1p.
  - Koht, H. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1926 May 22; 2p.
      (Enc: Oslo. Academia scientiarum norvegica. Sécretaire général. to Conseil internat. de recherches.
      Oslo. Norske videnskaps-academi i Oslo to Conseil internat. de recherches.
      Oslo. Norske videnskaps - i Oslo to Union académique internat.)
  - Kohut, G.A. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1933 June 15; 1p.
  - Koischwitz, Otto (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1933 June 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 June 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 July 14; 1p.
  - Kola Peninsula expedition (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1926 June
      - (See Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial, June 1926)
    - To S.A. Buturlin, 1927 Jan. 24
  - Kolar, Julia C. (Mrs. J.J.) (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 23; 2p.
  - Kolbe, Park R. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1920 July 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 May 25; 1p.
  - Kolbe, Walther (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 11; 1p.
  - Kolinski, Mierryslaw (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 29; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1932 May 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 May 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Apr. 12; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1933 June 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 June 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 May 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 June 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 July 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Sept. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 12
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 30; 2p.
  - Kolkin, N. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 28; 1p.
  - Koller, S. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 14; 1p.
  - Kollm, Georg (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1898 Nov. 3
  - Konenkova, Margarita (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1936 July 30; 2p.
  - Konig, Herbert (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 1; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 27; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Feb. 4; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Jan. 8; 7p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 1; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 14; postcard
    - To Boas
    - See Boas, F. open letter Mar. 22, 1923, 1923 May 3; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1923 June 12; 4p.
  - Konigbaum, A. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 26; receipt
  - Konow (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 26
  - Kopf, E.W. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1931 May 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 12; 1p.
  - Koppers, W. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 May 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 25; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 26; postcard
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 31; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1935 May 3; 2p.
      Letter by KAPPERS
  - Korbitz, R. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 20
    - To Boas, 1914 Nov. 20
  - Korchardt, Edwin (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1908 May 24
  - Korinetz, I. and Tsubin, E. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 30; 2p.
  - Korn, Mrs. Fannie Mayer (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 16; 1p.
  - Kornfeld, A.E. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 28; 1p.
  - Korr, I.M. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 8; 1p.
  - Korvalczyk, G. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1930 July 31; 1p.
  - Koschmieder, Elizabeth (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 21; 1p.
  - Koshkin, F.P. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1933 Jan. 20; 2p.
  - Koshkin, J.P. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 10; 1p.
  - Kosmos, Gesellschaft der Naturfruende (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 22
  - Kosok, P. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 26; 1p.
  - Kotschnig, Dr. Walter (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 16; 1p.
  - Kovarsky, Marcel (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 4; 1p.
  - Koy (Box 52)
    - Koy -- to A. Hansen, 1931 Dec.; 1p.
  - Krackwitzer, Mrs. E. (Box 52)
    - Mrs. E. Krackwitzer -- from H.O. Houghton & Co., undated
  - Kraeger, Heinrich (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 12; 1p.
    - H. Kraeger -- from Harry Pratt Judson, 1906 Aug. 29
  - Kraft, Erwin (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 14; 1p.
  - Kraft, J. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec.; 1p.
  - Kramer?? (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 4; 2p.
  - Kramer, Augustin (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1912 June 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1912 July 17
    - To Boas, 1912 July 27
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 30; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 19; 2p.
  - Kramer, Emil (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 28; 1p.
  - Kramer, F. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 27; 1p.
  - Kramer, Lucy (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1931 June 11; 5p.
    - (Enc. with Sargent, H.E., June 1931)
  - Krapp, G.P. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1919 May 14; 1p.
  - Kraske, Ilse (Box 52)
    - I. Kraske -- to Germanistic Soc. of America, 1931 June 5; 1p.
  - Kraus, A.J. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - See American Teacher, Feb. 1935
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 12; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 15; 1p.
    - See Provost, George Sept. 23, 1939., 1939 Oct. 3; 2p.
      See N.Y. Board of Higher Education.
    - Special Comm. Report..., Feb. 23, 1940.
    - (Enc. with Tead, O. Mar. 5, 1940), 1940 May 22; 1p.
    - (Enc: Kraus, A.J. to Roosevelt, F.D., 1940 May 20
      - Kraus, A.J. -- to NY College Teachers Union, 1940 May 20
    - Kraus, A.J. -- to NY College Teachers Union, 1940 May 20; 2p.
    - (Enc. with Kraus, A.J., May 22, 1940)
    - Kraus, A.J. -- to Roosevelt, F.D., 1940 May 20; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Kraus, A.J., May 22, 1940)
  - Kraus, defense committee (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1935 Feb.
  - Krause, Aurel (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1886 Mar. 3
    - To Boas, 1887 Feb. 23
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 17; card
    - To Boas, 1888 Aug. 27; card
    - To Boas, 1888 Dec. 17; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1890 Jan. 12; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1893 June 12; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1894 Sept. 10; card
  - Krause, F. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Sept. 27; 1p.
  - Krause, Fritz? (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Feb. 3; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 12; postcard
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 8; 1p.
      (Enc: List)
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 4; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Aug. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 June 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 July 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 July 25; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Sept. 10; 1p.
    - (Enc: Liste der in Leipzig wohnhaften Ethnologen), 1932 Sept. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec.; 15p.
    - F. Krause -- to L. Outhwaite, 1932 Nov. 14; 2p.
  - Krauss, Friedrich S. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1904 May 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 7
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1894 Nov. 27
    - To Boas, 1903 Mar. 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 May 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1903 May 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Mar. 11; postcard
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 23; postcard
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 8; postcard
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 6; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 15; postcard
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 6; postcard
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 9; 2p.
  - Krauss, T.S. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 12
  - Krauss, W. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 6; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Sept. 13; 3p.
  - Krausshaar?, Friedrich S. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1895 Jan. 1; 3p.
  - Kraut, B.N. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 26; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 4; 1p.
  - Krbecek, H.J. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1909 Oct. 20
  - Krebs, E. (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 19; 2p.
  - Krebs, N. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1927 Sept. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 May 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 July; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 18; 1p.
  - Krehbiel, Henry E. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1909 June 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1895 Dec. 20
    - To Boas, 1896 July 21
    - To Boas, 1897 July; 1p.
  - Krehler, Otto (Box 52)
    - To Boas, 1923 June 22; 2p.
  - Kremers, E. (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 17; 1p.
  - Kretschmer, Paul (Box 52)
    - From Boas, 1920 July 15; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1920 July 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 20; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 11; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 June 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 28; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 24; 6p.
    - To Boas, 1923 June 18; postcard
    - To Boas, 1930 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - P. Kretschmer -- to B.M. Headicar, 1920 June 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 July 16; 2p.
  - Kreuss? (Box 53)
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 20; 1p.
  - Kreutz (Box 53)
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 23; 1p.
  - Kreutzmann, Dr. Walter (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1937 Sept. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Sept. 27; 1p.
  - Kreykenbohm, D. (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 21; 1p.
  - Kriegel, Harvey G. (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 May 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 May 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 June 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 June 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 June 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 May 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 June 18; 1p.
  - Kriff, J.B. von? (Box 53)
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 13; 1p.
  - Kroeber, A.L. (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1903 May 1; 4p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 25; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1903 Dec. 11; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Feb. 18; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Mar. 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1904 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1904 May 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1904 May 25; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1904 July 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 May 25
    - From Boas, 1905 Oct. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 24
    - From Boas, 1906 May 24; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Sept. 18
    - From Boas, 1906 Sept. 24
    - From Boas, 1907 Jan. 23
    - From Boas, 1907 Feb. 4
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 20
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 27
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 19
    - From Boas, 1907 May 21
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 26
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 31
    - From Boas, 1907 Sept. 17
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 7
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 27
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 10; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 11
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 17
    - From Boas, 1907 Dec. 26
    - From Boas, 1908 Jan. 6; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Feb. 11
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 6; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 7
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 27
    - From Boas, 1908 Dec. 18
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 5
    - From Boas, 1909 Mar. 13
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 10; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1909 May 5
    - From Boas, 1909 June 10
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 26
    - From Boas, 1910 Mar. 19; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Nov. 29
    - From Boas, 1911 May 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 3
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 24; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 26
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 3
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 12; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 19
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 21
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 28; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Mar. 7; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 20
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1914 Dec. 1
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1916 May 22
    - (See Boas, F. to Gordon, G.B. May 22, 1916), 1916 Sept. 28
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 11
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 25
    - From Boas, 1916 Dec. 8
    - (See Boas, F. to Dixon, R.B. Dec. 8, 1916), 1917 Jan. 2
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 10
    - From Boas, 1917 Jan. 19; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 26; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Sept. 7; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1917 Sept. 14
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 18
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Sept. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Dec. 30; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Apr. 4; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Sept. 6; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Sept. 19; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 1; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 12; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 June 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Mar. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 30; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 May 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Apr. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 May 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Nov. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 May 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 May 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 June 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 June 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 July 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 July 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Sept. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 27; 5p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 5; telegram
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 1; telegram
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 15; telegram
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 21; telegram
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 May 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Aug. 5; 6p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 May 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 May 3; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. to Sapir, E., May 3, 1937.
    - From Boas, 1938 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 2; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 21; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1939 May 5; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. to Swadesh, M., June 22, 1939.
    - See Boas, F. to Bloomfield, L., Dec. 12, 1939.
    - See Boas, F. to Comm. on Amer. Indian Linguistics, Dec. 18, 1939.
    - See Boas, F. to Comm. on research on Amer. Indian Languages, Jan. 16, 1940.
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - (See Boas, F. to Comm. for research in Amer. Indian languages...Kroeber, Feb. 9, 1940)
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 29; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. to Comm. on Native Amer. Languages...Kroeber.., Apr. 29, 1940)
    - See Boas, F. to Comm. on Native Amer. Languages, May 31, 1940.
    - See Boas, F. to Bloomfield, July 31, 1940.
    - See Boas, F. to Swadesh, M., Feb. 6, 1941.
    - See Boas, F. to Hoijer, H., July 31, 1941.
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 19; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1942 July 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Sept. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Oct. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 May 8; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1904 May 25
    - To Boas, 1904 July 10
    - To Boas, 1905 May 24
    - To Boas, 1905 Aug. 25
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Nov. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 16
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 30
    - To Boas, 1906 May 15
    - To Boas, 1906 May 19
    - To Boas, 1906 May 21
    - To Boas, 1906 June 12
    - To Boas, 1906 June 13
    - To Boas, 1906 June 28
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 29
    - To Boas, 1906 Sept. 26
    - To Boas, 1906 Nov. 5
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 23
    - To Boas, 1907 Jan. 28
    - To Boas, 1907 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 20
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 8
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 11
    - To Boas, 1907 Sept. 8
    - To Boas, 1907 Sept. 21
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 31
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 9
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 3
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 11
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 16
    - To Boas, 1908 Jan. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1908 Feb. 1
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1908 Apr. 24
    - To Boas, 1908 May 5
    - To Boas, 1908 May 27
    - To Boas, 1908 Sept. 25
    - To Boas, 1908 Sept. 28
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 12
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 28
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 24
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 30
    - To Boas, 1909 Jan. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 15
    - To Boas, 1909 Mar. 19
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 30; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1909 May 14
    - To Boas, 1909 June 1
    - To Boas, 1909 June 4
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 4
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 9
    - To Boas, 1910 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1910 Mar. 2
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1911 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1911 May 6
    - To Boas, 1911 May 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 2
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 8